[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Ah, geez, I'm runnin' late!
PA: Good morning,
Who said that?!
PA: and welcome to the Black
Mesa Transit System.
Oh, it's the intercom.
PA: This automated train is provided
for the security and convenience...
Ah, I'm not the only one who's late.
SUCKER!
Ha hah!
PA: The time is 8:47 AM.
Shit!
I didn't know I was THAT late!
PA: Current topside temperature is
Oh, man...
PA: 93 degrees
8:47...
PA: with an estimated high of 105.
I am so dead.
PA: The Black Mesa Compound is maintained
Shit...
PA: at a pleasant 68 degrees
at all times.
I need to buy a watch; I'm already
on probation with the company.
They could fire me.
PA: This train is inbound from
Oh well!
PA: Level 3 Dormitories to
What can you do?
PA: Sector C Test Labs and
Control Facilities.
Bzzt!
PA: If your intended destination
PA: is a high-security area
High-security...
PA: beyond Sector C, you will need to
return to the Central Transit Hub in Area 9,
Am I on the right train?
PA: and board a high-security train.
PA: If you have not yet submitted your
identity to the Retinal Clearance System,
PA: you must report to
Oh!  What's this?
PA: Black Mesa personnel
PA: for processing before you
will be permitted
PA: into the High Security Branch
Huh... what...?
PA: of the Transit System.
Yeah, "High Security"!
That's why we leave armed missiles
lying around for everyone to check out.
It's part of the tour.
PA: Due to the high toxicity of material
routinely handled in the
Black Mesa Compound,
PA: no smoking, eating,
or drinking are permitted
PA: within the Black Mesa Transit System.
Fascists!
Yeah, whatever, I'll drink a
40-ounce up here if I feel like it.
PA: Please keep your limbs
inside the train at all times.
Yeah, well, I'll stick my arms
out the window if I-- Okay, maybe not.
PA: ...until the train has complete
halt at the station platform.
PA: In the event of an emergency,
passengers are to remain seated
and await further instruction.
Hey, what's going on there?
PA: If it is necessary to exit the train,
PA: disabled personnel should be
PA: evacuated first.
I should've been a pilot.
PA: Please, stay away from
electrified rails,
Hah!
PA: and proceed to an emergency station
Wow...
PA: until assistance arrives.
Man, how dumb would you have to be?
I mean, they're not gonna to say
something like that
unless somebody's already
tried to do it, right?
I guess if I was drunk enough, I
might climb out the window here
and pull some hangtime on the
electrified tram rail.
That kind of reminds me of that
squirrel that got caught
between the power lines
one day back at MIT.
The thing caught on fire and got
fused to the wires,
which caused a transformer to blow up
and knock out the power to all of campus.
That squirrel must've cost the
university at least $10,000.
That was a good day.
PA: A reminder that the Black
Mesa Hazard Course Decathlon
Oh man!
PA: will commence this evening
at 1900 hours
I forgot about that!
PA: at the Level 3 Facility.
PA: The semi-finals for High Security
Personnel will be announced
PA: in a separate
Secure Access Transmission.
I need to practice.
PA: Remember: more lives than
your own may depend on your fitness.
What? We're physicists.
PA: Do you have a friend or
relative who would make
PA: a valuable addition
to the Black Mesa Team?
I don't believe in friends.
PA: Immediate openings are
available in areas of:
PA: Materials Handling and
PA: Low-Clearance Security
Oh, cool! A robot!
Robots are the only friends I need.
PA: ...for further information.
Man!
PA: If you have an associate with a background
Look at that thing!
PA: in the areas of: theoretical physics,
Looks like a giant worker ant.
PA: biotechnology,
Man, robots rule!
PA: or other high-tech disciplines,
PA: please contact our
Pneumatics rule!
PA: Civilian Recruitment Division.
That's awesome.
PA: The Black Mesa Research Facility
is an equal-opportunity employer.
Man, they're still talking about hiring?
I guess my cousin Jessie needs a job.
If only he wasn't a sex-offender,
it would be so much easier to
find something for him.
PA: A reminder to all
Black Mesa Personnel:
PA: Regular radiation and
biohazard screenings
PA: are a requirement of
continued employment
PA: in the Black Mesa Research Facility
Bluh! Don't remind me.
PA: Missing a scheduled urinalysis or
PA: radiation checkup is grounds
Whoa...WE'RE GOING TO CRASH!
PA: for immediate termination.
PA: If you feel you have been
Oh, good, it stopped.
PA: exposed to radioactive or
other hazardous materials
What are YOU looking at?!
PA: in the course of your duties,
PA: contact your Radiation Safety Officer
PA: immediately.
Hey, what's that green crap?
PA: Work safe, work smart.
What is this?
PA: Your future depends on it.
Jesus Christ! Look at this place!
This is a DISASTER!
PA: Now arriving at
That's gotta be toxic.
PA: Sector C Test Labs and Control Facilities.
God, the EPA is going to tear us apart
if they find out about that.
Well, I'm not saying anything.
I don't want to get called into
court as a witness on this
once the cat gets out of the bag.
PA: Please stand back from the
automated door
PA: and wait for the security
officer to verify your identity.
Locked!
PA: Before exiting the train, be sure to
check your area for personal belongings.
Hm...
PA: Thank you, and have a very
safe and productive day.
GUARD: Morning, Mr. Freeman.
Looks like you're runnin' late.
Yeah, you know what? I don't
even care anymore.
By the time I get suited up, I'm
going to be over an hour late.
I figure, I'm either fired or I'm not.
Is someone following me?
Okay, good.
Yeah, I'm just going to stroll in there
like I own the damned place,
take my time, maybe get some doughnuts...
If I'm fired, I could probably jack some
office supplies or computer equipment
or something on the way out.
I could just stuff things in a big
duffel bag, nobody's going to notice.
Hmm, y'know, Steve's never in his cubicle.
I could just walk right up and
take his laptop.
Hell! I could grab that color laser printer
from Accounting. That thing's nice!
That's gotta be worth a couple
grand right there.
Huh, I wonder if it can print money...